American Association for Labor Legislation Records 5001
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
American Association for Labor Legislation Records
1905-1943
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
American Association for Labor Legislation
5001
57 cubic feet
57 linear ft.
Broadsides (notices), correspondence, records.
Records consist of correspondence, committee minutes, reports, financial records and research documents generated by staff members to facilitate legislative programs. These research materials deal with the following subjects: general labor law, general social insurance, health insurance, occupational safety, diseases and accidents, labor law administration, pensions and old age benefits, unemployment, wages, hours of work, working conditions, workers' compensation and unionism.
3336824
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, March 15, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 19, 2016
Biographical / Historical
CHRONOLOGY OF JOHN B. ANDREWS
1880: Born at South Wayne/ Lafayette County, Wisconsin, August 2
1904: A.B. from the University of Wisconsin
1905: A.M. from Dartmouth, Economics
1908: Ph.D. from University of Wisconsin, Economics
1909: Executive Secretary, member of Executive Committee, American Association of Labor Legislation, February 12
1910: Married Irene Osgood, August 8
1911: Founder and editor, American Labor Legislation Review (quarterly)
1913: Member Mayor's Committee on Unemployment (New York)
1919: U.S. Delegate to International Labor Office, Conferenc Geneva
1920: Lecturer on Social Legislation at Columbia; (also 192 1930, 1939)
1921: Member President's Unemployment Conference
1931: Member Pennsylvania Unemployment Commission
1932: Member New York Commission on Workmen's Compensation
1936: U.S. Delegate, International Labor Organization, Geneva
1937: Acting as consultant, Social Security Board
1938: Special Agent, U.S. Department of Labor
1939: Member Advisory Council, U.S. Employment Service
1943: Died, January 4
Biographical / Historical
The American Association for Labor Legislation was formed to promote uniformity of labor legislation and to encourage the study of labor conditions with a view toward promoting desirable legislation.
The Association was founded as a branch of the International Association for Labor Legislation. Preliminary discussions about forming the group occurred during 1905 and culminated in the first meeting of the Association held on February 15, 1906, in New York City.
During the Association's first few years, three basic objectives were established: to serve as the American branch of the International Association for Labor Legislation; to promote uniformity of labor legislation in the United States; and to encourage the study of labor conditions with a view toward promoting desirable labor legislation.
John Bertram Andrews was appointed executive secretary in 1909. His wife, Irene Osgood Andrews, eventually became associate secretary. John Andrews, as lobbyist, lecturer, author and editor of the publication The American Labor Legislation Review, became the motivating force of the Association. Broadly speaking, the American Association for Labor Legislation set the following goals: the alleviation of adverse working conditions; the creation of laws to protect safety and health on the job; and the provision of compensation in times of unemployment and benefits for workers no longer able to participate in the labor force. To facilitate the implementation of the Association's interests, study groups were established to investigate labor conditions. Active lobbying was undertaken in support of protective labor legislation in state and federal legislatures, and critiques were published concerning pending bills. The lifetime of the Association roughly corresponded to Andrews'
lifetime; its activities ceased after his death in 1943.
Scope and Contents
Records consist of correspondence, committee minutes, reports, financial records and research documents generated by staff members to facilitate legislative programs. These research materials deal with the following subjects: general labor law, general social insurance, health insurance, occupational safety, diseases and accidents, labor law administration, pensions and old age benefits, unemployment, wages, hours of work, working conditions, workers' compensation and unionism.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5001 mf: American Association for Labor Legislation Records on Microfilm 5001 PAM: American Association for Labor Legislation Pamphlet File 5002: American Association for Social Security Records
Child labor -- United States; Convict labor -- United States; Employment agencies -- United States; Depressions--1929--United States.; Factory inspection -- United States; Hours of labor -- United States; Industrial accidents -- United States; Industrial safety -- United States; Health insurance -- United States; Lobbyists; New Deal, 1933-1939.; Occupational diseases -- United States; Pensions -- United States; Social legislation -- United States -- Bibliography; Social security--United States.; Unemployment -- United States; Foreign workers -- Insurance -- United States; Anthrax; Child labor -- Law and legislation -- United States; Children -- Law and legislation -- United States; Coal mining industry -- Safety regulations -- United States; Compressed air industry -- United States -- State supervision; Employment agencies -- United States -- State supervision; Hours of labor -- Law and legislation -- United States; Industrial accidents -- United States; Industrial hygiene -- Law and legislation -- United States; Industrial relations -- United States -- State supervision; Industrial safety -- Law and legislation -- United States; Disability insurance -- Law and legislation -- United States; Health insurance -- Law and legislation -- Germany; Health insurance -- Law and legislation -- Great Britain; Health insurance -- Law and legislation -- United States; Life insurance -- United States; Unemployment insurance -- Law and legislation -- United States; Interstate commerce -- Law and legislation -- United States; Iron industry -- United States -- Taxation; Kern Bill; Working class -- Medical Examinations -- United States; Laboratory technicians -- Licenses -- United States; Lead industry workers -- United States -- Diseases and hygiene; Lead poisoning; Lungs -- Dust diseases -- Prevention; Management -- Employee participation -- United States; Match industry workers -- United States -- Diseases and hygiene; Migrant labor -- United States -- Insurance; Mine inspection -- Law and legislation -- United States; Mine inspection -- United States -- State supervision; Mine safety -- Law and legislation -- United States; National health insurance -- United States; Old age assistance -- United States -- State supervision; Pensions -- Agriculture -- United States; Pensions -- Law and legislation -- United States; Phosphorus -- Toxicology; Public welfare -- California -- State supervision; Public welfare -- New York (State) -- State supervision; Public welfare -- Pennsylvania -- State supervision; Public welfare -- United States; Radiation injuries; Silicosis; Social security -- Law and legislation -- United States; Steel industry and trade -- Taxation -- United States; Strikes and lockouts -- Law and legislation -- United States; Union labels -- United States; Unemployment insurance -- New York (State); Unemployment insurance -- Wisconsin; Unemployment -- Law and legislation -- United States; Vocational Rehabilitation -- Law and legislation -- United States; Wages -- Law and legislation -- United States; Wages -- Minimum wage -- Law and legislation -- United States; Wages -- Minimum wage -- United States; Wages -- Women -- Law and legislation -- United States; Walsh-Healy Bill.; Women -- Employment -- Law and legislation -- United States; Workers' compensation -- Civil service -- United States; Workers' compensation -- Law and legislation -- United States; Workers' compensation -- Merchant marine -- United States; Workers' compensation -- Railroads -- United States; Workers' compensation -- Stevedores -- United States; Workers' compensation -- United States; Working conditions -- Law and legislation -- United States; Working conditions -- United States; United States -- Economic policy -- 1933-1945; United States -- Economic policy -- To 1933; United States -- Emigration and immigration; Public works -- United States; Occupational diseases; Abbot, Grace. 1878-1936.; Addams, Jane. 1860-1935.; Adler, Felix. 1851-1933.; Alexander, Magnus W. (Magnus Washington), 1870-1932.; Allen, James E., 1911-; Almy, Frederic, 1858-1935.; Altmeyer, Arthur J. (Arthur Joseph), 1891-1972.; Anderson, Mary, 1872-1964.; Andrews, John B. (John Bertram), 1880-1943; Arnstein, Leo; Bain, H. Foster, 1872-1948.; Bakke, E. Wight. (Edward Wight), 1903-1971; Baldwin, Roger N. (Roger Nash), 1884-1981; Barnes, Charles B. (Charles Brinton), 1870-; Bauer, Stephen.; Beaman, Middleton.; Beck, James D.; Boudin, Leonard, 1912-1989; Boyle, James, 1853-1939; Brake, Edwin V.; Raushenbush, Elizabeth Brandeis; Brandeis, Louis Dembitz,1856-1941; Brandt, Lilian, 1873-; Breckinridge, Sophonisba Preston, 1866-1948.; Brown, Gerald W., (Gerald Wayne), 1939-; Bruere, Robert, (Robert Walter), 1876-1964; Burke, James T.; Cammer, Harold; Carlton, Frank T.; Cease, D. L.; Chadbourn, Thomas L. (Thomas Lincoln), 1871-; Chamberlain, Joseph P. (Joseph Perkins), 1873-1951.; Cheney, Howell, 1870-1957; Chlopek, Anthony; Chubb, Irene Sylvester; Clauson, Andrew; Clively, C.; Colby, Everett, 1897-1943.; Coman, Katharine, 1857-1915.; Commons, John R. (John Rogers), 1862-1945; Coulter, John L.; Count, George; Coyle, Grace Longwell, 1892-; Davies, Edgar T. (Edgar Thomas), 1873-; Dawson, Miles M. (Miles Menander), 1863-1942; De Leon, Solon, 1883-; Devine, Edward T. (Edward Thomas), 1867-1948; Dewey, Davis Rich, 1858-1942.; Doak, William Nuckles, 1882-1933; Dodd, Bella, 1904-1969; Dodd, Walter F.; Doten, Carroll (Carroll Warren), 1871-1942; Douglas, Dorothy J.; Douglas, Paul H. (Paul Howard), 1892-1976; Draper, Ernest Gallaudet, 1885-1954; Dreier, Mary E. (Mary Elisabeth), 1875-1963; Drown, Frank S.; Dummer, Mrs. W. F.; Eastman, Crystal, 1881-1928; Eaves, Lucile, 1869-; Eells, Howard P., 1855-1919; Ellinwood, Everett E., 1862-1943; Ely, Richard T. (Richard Theodore), 1854-1943; Epstein, Abraham, 1892-1942; Erskine, Lillian; Esch, John J. (John Jacob), 1861-1941; Evans, Elizabeth Glendower, 1856-1937; Faichild, Milton, 1865-1939; Farnam, Henry W. (Henry Walcott), 1853-1933; Fast, Howard, 1914-2003; Favill, Henry B.; Fisher, Irving, 1867-1947; Fitch, John A. (John Andrews), 1881- 1959; Fitzgerald, Roy G. (Roy Gerald), 1875-1962; Fletcher, Richard H.; Ford, Lucia O.; Frankel, Lee K. (Lee Kaufer), 1867-1931; Frankfurter, Felix, 1882-1965; Franklin, S. M.; Freund, Ernst, 1864-1932; Frey, John P. (John Philip), 1871-1957; Furuseth, Andrew, 1854-1938; Fuss, Henri; Fuster, Edward; Gellhorn, Walter, 1906- 1995; Gettemy, Charles F. (Charles Ferris), 1868-; Gilbreth, Frank Bunker, 1868-1924; Gilmore, C. Edwin; Glenn, John M.; Glicksman, Nathan; Golden, John; Goldmark, Josephine Clara, 1877-1950; Goldwater, S.S. (Sigismund Schulz), 1873-1942; Gompers, Samuel, 1850-1924; Gordon, Merritt J. b. 1857; Grant, Luke; Gray, John H. (John Henry), 1859-1946; Gray, R.S.; Green, William, 1872-1952; Hall, Fred S. (Fred Smith),1870-1946; Halsey, Olga; Hamilton, Alice, 1869-1970; Hammond, M. B. (Matthew Brown), 1868-1933; Handley, J. J.; Hanger, G. W. W. (Glossbrenner Wallace William), 1866-1935; Hard, William, 1878-1962; Harding, Warren G. (Warren Gamaliel), 1865-1923; Harper, C. A.; Harrington, Charles, 1865-1943; Harrington, D.; Hatch, L. W. (Leonard Williams), 1869-1958; Haynes, John Randolph; Haythorn, Samuel R.; Henderson, C. R.; Hendly, Charles; Hering, Frank (Frank Earl), 1874-1943; Higday, Hamilton; Hillman, Sidney, 1887-1946; Hoffman, Frederick L. (Frederick Ludwig), 1865-1946; Hohaus, Reinhard; Holbrook, Elmer Allen, 1881-1957; Hoover, Herbert, 1874-1964; Ickes, Harold L. (Harold LeClair), 1874-1952; Ingram, Frances; James, Margaret; Jansen, William; Jenks, J. W.; Johnson, Ethel M.; Judson, Frederick N. (Frederick Newton), 1845-1919; Kasten, Marie; Keating, Edward, 1875-1965; Kelley, Florence, 1859-1932; Kellogg, Arthur; Kellogg, Paul Underwood, 1879-1958; Kennedy, Thomas; Kingsbury, (Susan Myra), 1870-1949; Kirk, William; Kratz, John Aubel,1884-; La Follette, Robert M. (Robert Marion), 1895-1953; La Guardia, Fiorello H. (Fiorello Henry), 1882-1947; Lambert, Alexander, 1861-1939; Lapp, John A. (John Augustus), 1880-; Lathrop, Julia C.; Launer, William; Lazard, Max, 1875-; Leaderman, Abraham; Lee F.; Leeds, William M.; Lefkowitz, Abraham, 1884-1956; Lescohier, Don D. (Don Divance), 1883-1961; Lindsay, Samuel McCune, 1869-1960; Linville, Henry (Henry Richardson), 1866-1941; Lippmann, Walter, 1889-1974; London, Meyer, 1871-1926; Lorenz, Max, 1901-1975; Lovejoy, Owen R. (Owen Reed), 1866-1961; Low, Seth, 1850-1916; Lubin, Isador, 1896-1978; Lynch, James; Macy, V. E. (V. Everett); Magnusson, Leifur, 1882-; Mahon, W. A.; Mallery, Otto Tod, 1881-1956; Marburg, Theodore, 1862-1946; Marot, Helen, 1865-1940; Martin, John; Martindale, Frederick C.; McCall, Sidney; McCrea, Roswell C. (Roswell Cheney), 1876-1951; McDowell, Mary Elizabeth Smith, 1870-1897; McEwen, W. E.; McKelway, Alexander Jeffrey, 1866-1918; McKitrick, Reuben; Meany, George, 1894-1980; Meeker, Royal, 1873-1953; Mercer, H. V. (Hugh Victor); Meserole, Darwin J.; Metcalf, Henry C. (Henry Clayton), 1867-1942; Miller, Arthur, 1915-2005; Milner, Lucille, 1888-; Mitchell, Wesley C. (Wesley Clair), 1874-1948; Morgan, Anne; Morrison, Frank, 1859-1949; Moseley, Ned, 1846-1911; Moskowkitz, Henry L.; Munsterberg, Hugo, 1863-1916; Neill, Charles P. (Charles Patrick), 1865-1942; Nestor, Agnes, 1880-1948; Neustadt, Richard M.; Norris, George W. (George William). 1861-1944; Norton, J. Pease (John Pease), 1877; Noyes, Henry; O'Connor, T.V., 1870-1935; Osgood, Irene, b. 1879; Parkinson, Thomas J.; Parry, Carl E.; Peixotta, Jessica B. (Jessica Blanche), 1864-1941; Perkins, Frances, 1882-1965; Pierce, Paul S. (Paul Skeels); Pillsbury, A. J.; Pinchot, Gifford, 1865-1946; Plaisted, John W.; Polakov, Walter (Walter Nicholas), b. 1879; Price, C. W.; Rabinowitz, Victor; Raushenbush, Paul; Richards, C. R. (Charles Russell), 1865-1936; Robins, Margaret Dreier; Robins, Raymond, colonel; Robinson, Joseph Taylor. 1872-1937; Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich), 1908-1979; Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1884-1962; Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Franklin Delano), 1882-1945; Rubinow, I. M. (Isaac Max), 1875-1936; Russell, Rose; Ryan, Joseph; Sanford, Mary R.; Sanger, Sophy, 1881-1950; Schaffner, Margaret R.; Schneiderman, Rose, 1882-; Schram, Louis B.; Schwedtman, F. Charles (Ferdinand Charles), 1867-1952; Scott, Laura; Seager, Henry R. (Henry Roger), 1870-1930; Seligman, Eustace; Shapleigh, Elizabeth; Sherman, P. Tecumseh (Philemon Tecumseh), 1867-1941; Shillady, John R., 1875-1943; Smith, Alfred Emanuel, 1873-1944; Stern, Erich Cramer; Stewart, Ethelbert, 1857-1936; Stoddard, William Leavitt; Stone, Warren S. (Warren Sanford), 1860-1925; Strong, Josiah, 1847-1916; Style, H. Pillsbury; Swift, Wiley; Talbot, Ethelbert, 1848-1928; Tarbell, Ida M. (Ida Minerva), 1857-1944; Taussig, Frank William, 1859-1940; Taylor, Graham Romeym, 1880-1942; Taylor, Graham, 1851-1938; Thomas, Harry D.; Tolman, William Howe, 1861-; Trumbull, Millie R.; Van Kleeck, Mary, 1883-1972; Varlez, Louis, 1868-1930; Vaughan, Victor C. (Victor Clarence), 1851-1929; Verrill, Charles H. (Charles Henry); Wagner, Robert F. (Robert Ferdinand), 1877-1953; Wald, Lillian D., 1867-1940; Walker, John Hunter, 1872-1955; Watrous, Paul H.; Weber, Adna Ferrin, 1870-1968; Wesbrook, F. F. (Frank Fairchild), 1868-1918; Wilcox, Frederick (Frederick Bernon), 1879-1965; Wiley, Katherine; Winant, John Gilbert (John Gilbert), 1889-1947; Wise, Stephen; Witt, Nathan; Witte, Edwin E. (Edwin Emil), 1887-1960; Wolman, Leo, 1890-1961; Woodbury, Helen Sumner, 1876-1933; Woodruff, Clinton Rogers, 1868-1948; Wright, Edwin R.; Zelman, Benjamin; Zitron, Abraham; Amalgamated Association of Street and Electric Railway Employees of America; Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America; American Association for Labor Legislation; American Association for Old Age Security; American Association for Social Security; American Association for the Advancement of Science; American Association 
3336824
- Correspondence (Weber), 1905 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Photos of Mr. and Mrs. Andrews (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Scope and Contents
  No date
- Correspondence (Weber), 1906 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1907 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  January 1-31, 1908
- Correspondence, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  February 1-29, 1908
- Correspondence, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  March 2-13, 1908
- Correspondence, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  March 14-19, 1908
- Correspondence, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  March 20-31, 1908
- Correspondence, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  April 1-7, 1908
- Correspondence, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  April 8-13, 1908
- Correspondence, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  April 14-22, 1908
- Correspondence, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  April 23-30, 1908
- Correspondence, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  May 2-9, 1908
- Correspondence, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  May 11-15, 1908
- Correspondence, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  May 16-22, 1908
- Correspondence, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  May 23-30, 1908
- Correspondence, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  June 1-30, 1908
- Correspondence, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  July 2-20, 1908
- Correspondence, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  July 22-31, 1908
- Correspondence, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  August 1-14, 1908
- Correspondence, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  August 15-27, 1908
- Correspondence, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  September 1-30, 1908
- Correspondence, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  October 1-9, 1908
- Correspondence, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  October 10-13, 1908
- Correspondence, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  October 14-19, 1908
- Correspondence, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  October 20-23, 1908
- Correspondence, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  October 24-31, 1908
- Correspondence, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  November 1-7, 1908
- Correspondence, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  November 9-12, 1908
- Correspondence, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  November 13-16, 1908
- Correspondence, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  November 17-21, 1908
- Correspondence, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  November 23-30, 1908
- Correspondence, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  December 1-3, 1908
- Correspondence, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  December 4-9, 1908
- Correspondence, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  December 10-16, 1908
- Correspondence, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  December 17-18, 1908
- Correspondence, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  December 19-29, 1908
- Correspondence, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  No specific dates.
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  January 1-11, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  January 12-18, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  January 19-21, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  January 22-25, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  January 26-28, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  January 29-30, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  February 1-4, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  February 5-9, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  February 10-14, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  February 15-19, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  February 20-27, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  March 1-5, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  March 6-10, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  March 11-14, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  March 15-17, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  March 18-20, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  March 22-23, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  March 24-25, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  March 26-27 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  March 29-31, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  April 1-6, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  April 7-15, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  April 16-20, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  April 21-24, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  April 26-30, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  May 1-6, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  May 7-10, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  May 11-13, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  May 14-16, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  May 17-19, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  May 20-22, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  May 24-26, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  May 27-28, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  May 29-31, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  June 1-3, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  June 4-7, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  June 8-10, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  June 11-14, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  June 15-18, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  June 19-21, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  June 22-24, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  June 25-28, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  June 29-30, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  July 3-29, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  August 3-30, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  September 4-30, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  October 1-29, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  November 1-29, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  December 8-27, 1909
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  January 1-5, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  January 6-9, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  January 10-12, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  January 13-17, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  January 18-21, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  January 22-25, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  January 26-31, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  February 1-7, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  February 8-13, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  February 14-18, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  February 19-21, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  February 22-24, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  February 25-28, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  March 1-3, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  March 4-5, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  March 7-8, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  March 9-10, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  March 11-12, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  March 14-15, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  March 16-18, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  March 19, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  March 20-22, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  March 23-25, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 31)